A Guide to the Christopher C. Kraft Papers, 1941-1982
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- 1972
  - Results of Public Opinion Survey Re: Space Program c.1972 (Box-folder 17-42)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 17-43)
- 1973
  - Kiwanas Club, Houston TX, speech, January 31, 1973 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - Personal Notes, January 1973 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - University of Houston, speech, February 10, 1973 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - Delaware NSPE speech, Wilmington, DE, February 20, 1973 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - Personal Notes, February 1973 (Box-folder 18-5)
  - Skylab Supplement, Mission Operation Report, March 1, 1973 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - Goddard Memorial Dinner, March 9, 1973 (Box-folder 18-7)
  - Apollo 17 Mission Report, March 1973 (Box-folder 18-8)
  - Personal Notes, March 1973 (Box-folder 18-9)
  - Personal Notes, April 1973 (Box-folder 18-10)
  - Mannual for 70mm Hand-Held Photography from SkyLab, May 1973 (Box-folder 18-11)
  - Personal Notes, May 1973 (Box-folder 18-12)
  - Kraft Interview by Jones, June 12, 1973 (Box-folder 18-13)
  - Personal Notes, June 1973 (Box-folder 18-14)
  - Personal Notes, July 1973 (Box-folder 18-15)
  - Kraft Interview by E.M. Emme and Grimwood, August 20, 1973 (Box-folder 18-16)
  - Meeting with Oil Company Executives, August 28, 1973 (Box-folder 18-17)
  - Clear Lake Chamber of Commerce Speech, August 30, 1973 (Box-folder 18-18)
  - Personal Notes, August 1973 (Box-folder 18-19)
  - Personal Notes, September 1973 (Box-folder 18-20)
  - SkyLab 3 Debriefing Notes, October 3, 1973 (Box-folder 18-21)
  - Town Hall Speech, West LA, California, October 5, 1973 (Box-folder 18-22)
  - National Association of Cemeteries Conference, October 23, 1973 (Box-folder 18-23)
  - Earth Observations From Space: Outlook for the Geological Sciences, October 1973 (Box-folder 18-24)
  - Evolution of the Earth's Crust, October 1973 (Box-folder 18-25)
  - Personal Notes, October 1973 (Box-folder 18-26)
  - Apollo 17 Technical Debriefing, January 4, 1973 (Box-folder 18-27)
  - National Audio-Visual Association Speech, January 20, 1973 (Box-folder 18-28)
  - 1973 ASME Medal Award, November 14, 1973 (Box-folder 18-29)
  - Houston Chapter of Texas C.P.A's speech, November 28,1973 (Box-folder 18-30)
  - Personal Notes, November 1973 (Box-folder 18-31)
  - Personal Notes, December 1973 (Box-folder 18-32)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 18-33)
  - Reference Material for CCK Speeches, 1973 (Box-folder 18-34)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence 1973 (Box-folder 18-35)
- 1974
  - Personal Notes, January 1974 (Box-folder 18-36)
  - Skylab Mission Report, Second Visit, January 1974 (Box-folder 18-37)
  - Engineer of the Year, San Fernando Valley Engineers Council, February 23, 1974 (Box-folder 18-38)
  - Personal Notes, February 1974 (Box-folder 18-39)
  - Goddard Memorial Dinner, 1974 (Box-folder 18-40)
  - BOEING 747 Shuttle Carrier Documents, March 1974 (Box-folder 18-41)
  - Personal Notes, March 1974 (Box-folder 18-42)
  - Personal Notes, April 1974 (Box-folder 18-43)
  - Founders' Day Speech, April 12, 1974 (Box-folder 18-44)
  - Shuttle Avionics Block Diagram, April 30, 1974 (Box-folder 18-45)
  - Personal Notes, May 1974 (Box-folder 18-46)
  - Personal Notes,June 1974 (Box-folder 19-1)
  - 3rd International Aviation Conference, July 3, 1974 (Box-folder 19-2)
  - Skylab Mission Report, June 1974 (Box-folder 19-3)
  - IBM Seminar - Sands Point, July 16, 1974 (Box-folder 19-4)
  - Grumann [Review for CCK] Bethpage, NY, July 16, 1974 (Box-folder 19-5)
  - Personal Notes, July 1974 (Box-folder 19-6)
  - SkyLab Mission Report - Third Visit, July 1974 (Box-folder 19-8)
  - Skylab Mission Report Supplement 3, Flight Crew Contributions, July 1974 (Box-folder 19-9)
  - Personal Notes, August 1974 (Box-folder 19-10)
  - National Agricultural Chemicals Association Speech, September 30, 1974 (Box-folder 19-11)
  - Personal Notes, September 1974 (Box-folder 19-12)
  - Interview with Working Group "Outlook for Space" Study, October 1974 (Box-folder 19-13)
  - Personal Notes, October 1974 (Box-folder 19-14)
  - Personal Notes, November 1974 (Box-folder 19-15)
  - Personal Notes, December 1974 (Box-folder 19-16)
  - George Low Interview By Robert Sherrod, 1974 (Box-folder 19-17)
  - Personal Correspondene, 1974 (Box-folder 19-18)
  - Reference Material for CCK Speches, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 19-19)
  - Personal Notes, January 1974 (Box-folder 19-20)
- 1975
  - Personal Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 19-7)
  - Personal Notes, February 1975 (Box-folder 19-21)
  - Personal Notes, March 1975 (Box-folder 19-22)
  - Apollo Program Summary Report, April 1975 (Box-folder 19-23)
  - Personal Notes, April 1975 (Box-folder 19-24)
  - Houston Rotary Club Speech, May 29, 1975 (Box-folder 19-25)
  - Personal Notes, May 1975 (Box-folder 19-26)
  - Personal Notes, June 1975 (Box-folder 19-27)
  - Personal Notes, July 1975 (Box-folder 19-28)
  - ASTP Technical Crew Debriefing, August 8, 1975 (Box-folder 19-30)
  - Personal Notes, September 1975 (Box-folder 19-31)
  - International Assoicaiation of Hospitality Accountants, September 19, 1975 (Box-folder 19-32)
  - International Academy of Aviation and Space Medicine, October 6, 1975 (Box-folder 19-34)
  - American Women's Society of CPAs, October 10, 1975 (Box-folder 19-35)
  - Personal Notes, October 1975 (Box-folder 19-36)
  - Speech at Valley Forward Association, Phoenix, November 18, 1975 (Box-folder 20-1)
  - Personal Notes, November 1975 (Box-folder 20-2)
  - Apollo Soyuz Mission Evaluation Report, December 1975 (Box-folder 20-3)
  - Personal Notes, December 1975 (Box-folder 20-4)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 20-5)
  - Proposed Organization of IMCC Project Office, 1975 (Box-folder 20-6)
  - List of CCK Speeches, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 26-38)
- 1976
  - CCK Article "Computers and the Space Program: An Overview," January 1976 (Box-folder 20-7)
  - Personal Notes, January 1976 (Box-folder 20-8)
  - Space Center Rotary Club, Houston, January 5, 1976 (Box-folder 20-9)
  - Jockey International speech, February 3, 1976 (Box-folder 20-10)
  - Gulfway (Houston) Rotary Club, February 26, 1976 (Box-folder 20-11)
  - Personal Notes, February 1976 (Box-folder 20-12)
  - Texas A&M College of Engineering, March 9, 1976 (Box-folder 20-13)
  - Downtown Optimist Club, Houston, February 19,1976 (Box-folder 20-14)
  - Aerojet Booster Club, Sacremento, March 16, 1976 (Box-folder 20-15)
  - National Downtowner Franchise Conference, Charlotte N.C., March 28, 1976 (Box-folder 20-16)
  - Kraft Interview by Edward Ezell, March 28, 1976 (Box-folder 20-17)
  - Personal Notes, March 1976 (Box-folder 20-18)
  - Kraft Interview by Edward Ezell, April 12, 1976 (Box-folder 20-19)
  - Airforce Association Symposium, Vandenburg Air Force Base, April 29, 1976 (Box-folder 20-20)
  - Executive Commitee of Houston Chamber of Commerce, April 20, 1976 (Box-folder 20-21)
  - Personal Notes, April 1976 (Box-folder 20-22)
  - W.R.Grace & Co., Amelia Island, May 18, 1976 (Box-folder 20-23)
  - Informal Discussion with Local Businessmen's Group, May 27, 1976 (Box-folder 20-24)
  - Listing of Material in NASA Science & Technology Information Facility, May 5, 1976 (Box-folder 20-25)
  - Personal Notes, May 1976 (Box-folder 20-26)
  - Material for CCK Story in DuPont Magazine, May-June 1976 (Box-folder 20-27)
  - Material for CCK Story in Houston Magazine, June 1976 (Box-folder 20-28)
  - Personal Correspondence: Incoming, January-June 1976 (Box-folder 20-29)
  - Personal Correspondence: Outgoing, January-June 1976 (Box-folder 20-30)
  - Personal Notes, June 1976 (Box-folder 20-32)
  - Board of Directors, Houston Chamber of Commerce, July 13, 1976 (Box-folder 20-32)
  - Personal Notes, July 1976 (Box-folder 20-33)
  - KRTH Radio Interviewsk Frank Haley Show, August 17, 1976 (Box-folder 20-34)
  - Harris County Association of Mayors and Councilmen, August 19, 1976 (Box-folder 20-35)
  - Breakfast Club at River Oaks Country Club, August 25, 1976 (Box-folder 20-36)
  - Personal Notes, August 1976 (Box-folder 20-37)
  - Purchasing Management Association, Houston, September 14, 1976 (Box-folder 20-38)
  - Speech at University of St. Thomas, Houston, September 28, 1976 (Box-folder 20-39)
  - Personal Notes, September 1976 (Box-folder 20-40)
  - French Legion of Honour, October 13, 1976 (Box-folder 20-41)
  - Wings Club NYC, October 19, 1976 (Box-folder 20-42)
  - Personal Notes, October 1976 (Box-folder 20-43)
  - The Conference Board Speech, Houston, November, 3, 1976 (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Aviation Week Special Issue on Shuttle, November 8, 1976 (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Career Service Award - National Civil Service League, November 16, 1976 (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Personal Notes, November 1976 (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Young Presidents Organization, Speech, Dallas, December 14, 1976 (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Personal Notes, December 1976 (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Personal Correspondence, July - December 1976 (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Personal Correspondence- Outgoing, July - December 1976 (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 21-9)
  - CCK's Predictions of Development for the next 100 Years, For the CLC Time Capsule, 1976 (Box-folder 21-10)
  - CCK Speech Reference Material, 1976 (Box-folder 21-11)
- 1977
  - CCK Speech Reference Material, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 21-12)
  - Personal Notes, January 1977 (Box-folder 21-13)
  - Personal Notes, February 1977 (Box-folder 21-14)
  - Young President's Organization, Houston, March 22, 1977 (Box-folder 21-15)
  - Personal Notes, March 1977 (Box-folder 21-16)
  - Dr. Fletcher's Retirement Luncheon, speech, April 21, 1977 (Box-folder 21-17)
  - Tejas Chapter of DAR, Speech, Houston, April 26,1977 (Box-folder 21-18)
  - Aviation/Space Writers Speech, Ames, April 28, 1977 (Box-folder 21-19)
  - Personal Notes, April 1977 (Box-folder 21-20)
  - Southern Regional Ed. Board Speech, June 23, 1977 (Box-folder 21-22)
  - Incoming Personal Correspondence, January-June 1977 (Box-folder 21-24)
  - Outgoing Personal Correspondence, January-June 1977 (Box-folder 21-25)
  - Personal Notes, July 1977 (Box-folder 21-26)
  - California Space Day Speech, Los Angeles, August 11, 1977 (Box-folder 21-27)
  - KTRH Q/A Show, Jimm Bell, August 30,1977 (Box-folder 21-28)
  - Personal Notes, August 1977 (Box-folder 21-29)
  - Conference Board Speech, Caramel, September 9, 1977 (Box-folder 21-30)
  - Speech- Park Plaza Hospital Staff, Houston, September 20, 1977 (Box-folder 21-31)
  - Speech - Gen. Smith & Group of Dallas Businessmen, September 27, 1977 (Box-folder 21-32)
  - Personal Notes, September 1977 (Box-folder 21-33)
  - Personal Notes, October 1977 (Box-folder 21-35)
  - Cleveland Young Presidents Organization Speech, November 10, 1977 (Box-folder 21-36)
  - Personal Notes, November 1977 (Box-folder 21-37)
  - Council for Energy Studies Speech, Honolulu, HI, November 30 - December 2, 1977 (Box-folder 21-38)
  - Personal Notes, December 1977 (Box-folder 22-1)
  - Personal Incoming Correspondence, July-December 1977 (Box-folder 22-2)
  - Personal Outgoing Correspondence, July-December 1977 (Box-folder 22-3)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence 1977 (Box-folder 22-4)
- 1978
  - Space Center Rotary Club, January 1978 (Box-folder 22-5)
  - Personal Notes, January 1978 (Box-folder 22-6)
  - Midwest Research Institute, K.C., January 19, 1978 (Box-folder 22-7)
  - Diamond Shamrock Speech, January 24, 1978 (Box-folder 22-8)
  - Financial Analyst Federation, February 6, 1978 (Box-folder 22-9)
  - Houston TV Channel 8, February 17, 1978 (Box-folder 22-10)
  - National Black History Week, February 17, 1978 (Box-folder 22-11)
  - General Dynamics Executives, February 22, 1978 (Box-folder 22-12)
  - Personal Notes, February 1978 (Box-folder 22-13)
  - Energy Conference, Houston, March 23, 1978 (Box-folder 22-14)
  - Texas A and M, College Station, March 28, 1978 (Box-folder 22-15)
  - National Feed and Grain, Phoenix, March 29,1978 (Box-folder 22-16)
  - Personal Notes, March 1978 (Box-folder 22-17)
  - Continental Bank, April 10, 1978 (Box-folder 22-18)
  - Texas Commerce Bankshares, Houston, April18,1978 (Box-folder 22-20)
  - University of Houston at Clear Lake City, April 4, 1978 (Box-folder 22-20)
  - Federal Women's Week, April 17, 1978 (Box-folder 22-21)
  - Northwestern Bell, Board of Directors, April 27,1978 (Box-folder 22-22)
  - Personal Notes, April 1978 (Box-folder 22-23)
  - Texaco Round Table, White Plains, May 4, 1978 (Box-folder 22-24)
  - Cincinnati YPO, May 8, 1978 (Box-folder 22-25)
  - Biomed/ Life Sciences Conference, Houston, May 23, 1978 (Box-folder 22-26)
  - Instrument Society of America, Houston, May 23, 1978 (Box-folder 22-27)
  - Personal Notes, May 1978 (Box-folder 22-28)
  - Texas Society of Association Executives, Houston, June 10, 1978 (Box-folder 22-29)
  - Incoming Personal Mail, January-June 1978 (Box-folder 22-30)
  - Grocery Manufacteres of America, Greenbriar, June 19, 1978 (Box-folder 22-31)
  - Men's Forum, Houston Club, June 28, 1978 (Box-folder 22-32)
  - Personal Notes, June 1978 (Box-folder 22-33)
  - Outgoing Mail, January-June 1978 (Box-folder 22-34)
  - Opening of Baybrook Mall, Friendswood, July 26, 1978 (Box-folder 22-35)
  - Personal Notes, July 1978 (Box-folder 22-36)
  - Personal Notes, August 1978 (Box-folder 22-37)
  - U.S. Air Force Academy, Denver, September 26, 1978 (Box-folder 22-38)
  - Personal Notes, September 1978 (Box-folder 22-39)
  - Pasadena Texas Rotary, October 13, 1978 (Box-folder 22-40)
  - YPO Southern Conference, West Palm Beach October 18-21, 1978 (Box-folder 22-41)
  - Welcome Speech, Lacie Symposium, October 23, 1978 (Box-folder 22-42)
  - Personal Notes, October 1978 (Box-folder 22-43)
  - AAS Meetings Houston, November 1, 1978 (Box-folder 23-1)
  - AIAA/RAS Energy Conference, London, England, December 5-7, 1978 (Box-folder 23-2)
  - NASA Awards Ceremony, November 1, 1978 (Box-folder 23-3)
  - Personal Notes, November 1978 (Box-folder 23-4)
  - Personal Notes, December 1978 (Box-folder 23-5)
  - Incoming Mail, July-December 1978 (Box-folder 23-6)
  - Personal Outgoing, July-December 1978 (Box-folder 23-7)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 23-8)
- 1979
  - Welcome AAAS Meetings, Houston, January 3-8, 1979 (Box-folder 23-9)
  - Little Rock YPO, January 11, 1979 (Box-folder 23-10)
  - Rice University Speech, Houston, January 16, 1979 (Box-folder 23-11)
  - Personal Notes, January 1979 (Box-folder 23-12)
  - JSC Honor Awards, January 29,1979 (Box-folder 23-13)
  - Personal Notes, February 1979 (Box-folder 23-14)
  - Personal Notes, March 1979 (Box-folder 23-15)
  - Von Karman Lectureship AIAA, Washington D.C., February 6, 1979 (Box-folder 23-16)
  - YPO "University", Acapulco, February 25- March 3, 1979 (Box-folder 23-18)
  - Black History Week, February 16, 1979 (Box-folder 23-17)
  - Personal Notes, April 1979 (Box-folder 23-19)
  - Goddard Memorial Trophy, National Space Club, May 30, 1979 (Box-folder 23-20)
  - English Speaking Union, Houston, April 26, 1979 (Box-folder 23-21)
  - Personal Notes, May 1979 (Box-folder 23-22)
  - Roger W. Jones Award, American University, May 12, 1979 (Box-folder 23-23)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Villanova, May 1979 (Box-folder 23-24)
  - Personal Notes, June 1979 (Box-folder 23-25)
  - Personal Incoming, January- June 1979 (Box-folder 23-26)
  - Personal Outgoing, January-June 1979 (Box-folder 23-27)
  - Personal Notes, July 1979 (Box-folder 23-28)
  - 10th Anniversary Lunar Curatorial Facility, July 20, 1979 (Box-folder 23-29)
  - Personal Notes, August 1979 (Box-folder 23-30)
  - Texas Power and Light, Dallas, August 10, 1979 (Box-folder 23-31)
  - American BAR Association, Dallas, August 14, 1979 (Box-folder 23-32)
  - Columbus, Ohio YPO, September 10, 1979 (Box-folder 24-1)
  - Personal Notes, September 1979 (Box-folder 24-2)
  - Aerospace Medical Association, Galveston, TX, September 28, 1979 (Box-folder 24-3)
  - Personal Notes, October 1979 (Box-folder 24-4)
  - UPI, Houston, October 9, 1979 (Box-folder 24-5)
  - Induction to VA Aviation Hall of Fame, October 13, 1979 (Box-folder 24-6)
  - National Management Association Speech, October 18, 1979 (Box-folder 24-7)
  - National Security Industrial Association L.A., October 31, 1979 (Box-folder 24-8)
  - AAS, L.A., November 1, 1979 (Box-folder 24-9)
  - Personal Notes, November 1979 (Box-folder 24-10)
  - VA Women's Forum, Richmond, November 19, 1979 (Box-folder 24-11)
  - Rockwell Annual Management Meeting, Pheonix AZ, November 20, 1979 (Box-folder 24-12)
  - Meeting with Beale, Anderson, Jeffs, Yardlet, Lovelace, and Kraft, December 15, 1979 (Box-folder 24-13)
  - Personal Notes, December 1979 (Box-folder 24-14)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder 24-15)
  - Guest Book #1 with transcript of Guests, 1979 (Box-folder 24-16)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, July-December 1979 (Box-folder 24-17)
  - Incoming Correspondence, July-December 1979 (Box-folder 24-18)
  - Index to NASA News Release and Speeches, 1978 Supplement, 1979 (Box-folder 24-19)
- 1980
  - Personal Notes, January 1980 (Box-folder 24-20)
  - IBM MGT Group Holiday Inn, January 23, 1980 (Box-folder 24-21)
  - National Academy of Engineering, February 3, 1980 (Box-folder 24-23)
  - Personal Notes, February 1980 (Box-folder 24-22)
  - Women in Aviation and Space Symposium, March 12, 1980 (Box-folder 24-24)
  - River Oaks Professional Women's Breakfast Club, March 20, 1980 (Box-folder 24-25)
  - Personal Notes, March 1980 (Box-folder 24-26)
  - NASA and JSC Awards, March 25, 1980 (Box-folder 24-27)
  - Commercial Club of Chicago, March 22, 1980 (Box-folder 24-28)
  - Gossamer Albatross Opening Ceremony, April 3, 1980 (Box-folder 24-29)
  - Personal Notes, April 1980 (Box-folder 24-30)
  - "The Kissinger Doctrine", H.A.K Address, April 10, 1980 (Box-folder 24-31)
  - Personal Notes, May 1980 (Box-folder 24-32)
  - Space Shuttle System Summary, May 1980 (Box-folder 24-33)
  - Personal Notes, June 1980 (Box-folder 24-34)
  - Batelle Report: Orbiter TPS Strength Integrity, June 16, 1980 (Box-folder 24-35)
  - Incoming Correspondence, January-June 1980 (Box-folder 24-36)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, January -June 1980 (Box-folder 24-37)
  - Personal Notes, July 1980 (Box-folder 24-38)
  - Airforce Scientific Adv. Board, July 17, 1980 (Box-folder 24-39)
  - Tandem Elevon Actuator/ Enhanced Reliability, July 1980 (Box-folder 24-40)
  - High Pressure O2 Systems Review, August 1980 (Box-folder 24-41)
  - Personal Notes, August 1980 (Box-folder 24-42)
  - Presidential Distinguished Executive Award, September 9, 1980 (Box-folder 25-2)
  - Combined Loads Orbiter Test Status, September 12, 1980 (Box-folder 25-3)
  - OSTS Shuttle Program Review, September 4, 1980 (Box-folder 25-1)
  - Orbiter Component Loads Assessment, September 12, 1980 (Box-folder 25-4)
  - Hispanic Heritage Week, Welcome, September 19, 1980 (Box-folder 25-5)
  - Personal Notes, September 1980 (Box-folder 25-6)
  - SAE Keynote Address, LA, October 14, 1980 (Box-folder 25-7)
  - Personal Notes, October 19, 1980 (Box-folder 25-8)
  - Correspondence with Vice President George Bush, November 10, 1980 (Box-folder 25-9)
  - Personal Notes, November 1980 (Box-folder 25-10)
  - National Telecommunication Conference, December 1, 1980 (Box-folder 25-11)
  - On-Orbit TPS INSP and Repair System, December 12, 1980 (Box-folder 25-12)
  - Personal Notes, December 1980 (Box-folder 25-13)
  - Incoming Correspondence, July- December 1980 (Box-folder 25-14)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, July-December 1980 (Box-folder 25-15)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 25-16)
  - Orbital Thermal Protection Subsystem, 1980 (Box-folder 25-17)
  - Retro-Glide Booster Concept, ca.1980 (Box-folder 25-18)
  - Guest Book #2 (Signatures) & Typed List of Guests, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 26-37)
  - Miscellaneous Space Shuttle notes, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 26-40)
  - Reference Material for CCK Speeches, ca.1980 (Box-folder 26-39)
- 1981
  - Atlantic Richfield, Houston, January 6, 1981 (Box-folder 25-19)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 25-203)
  - Avionics Software Test Readiness, January 19, 1981 (Box-folder 25-21)
  - System Integration FRF/FRR Board for STS-1, January 21, 1981 (Box-folder 25-22)
  - OV-102 Analysis RE STS-1, January 20, 1981 (Box-folder 25-23)
  - STS-1 FRF Test Readiness Review, January 21, 1981 (Box-folder 25-24)
  - FRF Level II/I Presentation, January 22, 1981 (Box-folder 25-25)
  - STS-1 Launch/Landing OP's Review, January 23, 1981 (Box-folder 25-26)
  - Personal Notes, January 1981 (Box-folder 25-27)
  - VPI Committee of 100, January 1981 (Box-folder 25-28)
  - Personal Notes, February 1981 (Box-folder 25-29)
  - CCK Article "Renaissance of MSF," February 1981 (Box-folder 25-30)
  - Lunar Science Conference, March 16, 1981 (Box-folder 25-31)
  - Personal Notes, March 1981 (Box-folder 25-32)
  - VPI Alumni Distinguished Service Award, April 3, 1981 (Box-folder 25-33)
  - National Secretaries Week, April 20, 1981 (Box-folder 25-34)
  - Notes, STS-1 Debriefing to Management, April 22, 1981 (Box-folder 25-35)
  - Personal Notes, April 1981 (Box-folder 25-36)
  - Tejas Breakfast Club, May 7, 1981 (Box-folder 25-37)
  - White House Luncheon Invitees, May 19, 1981 (Box-folder 25-38)
  - Wichita YPO, May 21, 1981 (Box-folder 25-39)
  - Houston Kiwanis, May 27, 1981 (Box-folder 25-40)
  - Personal Notes, May 1981 (Box-folder 25-41)
  - Park Plaza Hospital Quarterly Meeting, June 2, 1981 (Box-folder 25-42)
  - VPI Interview for "Engineering Now," June 1981 (Box-folder 25-43)
  - Personal Notes, June 1981 (Box-folder 25-44)
  - Personal Correspondence: Incoming, June 1981 (Box-folder 25-45)
  - Personal Correspondence: Outgoing, January- June 1981 (Box-folder 25-46)
  - Dedication of Teague Auditorium, July 20, 1981 (Box-folder 25-47)
  - Personal Notes, July 1981 (Box-folder 25-48)
  - YPO Groups in Tokyo and Hong Kong: August 20-30, 1981 (Box-folder 25-49)
  - Miscellaneous photos, certificates, etc., 1958-? (Box-folder 26-1)
  - Personal Notes, August 1981 (Box-folder 26-2)
  - STS-1 Orbiter Final Mission Report, August 1981 (Box-folder 26-3)
  - STS-1 Honor Awards Ceremony, September 11, 1981 (Box-folder 26-4)
  - Personal Notes, September 1981 (Box-folder 26-5)
  - EMU/POS Manpower, April-September 1981 (Box-folder 26-6)
  - National Wholesale Furniture Association, High Point, October 23, 1981 (Box-folder 26-7)
  - Personal Notes, October 1981 (Box-folder 26-8)
  - Notes, STS-2 Debriefing, November 19, 1981 (Box-folder 26-9)
  - Bonneville Knife and Fork Club, Salt Lake City, November 19-20, 1981 (Box-folder 26-10)
  - Personal Notes, November 1981 (Box-folder 26-11)
  - Incoming Correspondence, July-December 1981 (Box-folder 26-12)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, July-December 1981 (Box-folder 26-13)
  - Personal Notes, December 1981 (Box-folder 26-14)
- 1982
  - Downtown Rotary and Joint OPO/YPO Meeting, Kansas City, January 14, 1982 (Box-folder 26-15)
  - Shreveport Chamber of Commerce, January 21, 1982 (Box-folder 26-16)
  - Personal Notes, January 1982 (Box-folder 26-17)
  - Welcome Houston Chamber of Commerce Executive Committee, February 4, 1982 (Box-folder 26-18)
  - Guest Professor at Rice University, February 29, 1982 (Box-folder 26-19)
  - Personal Notes, February 1982 (Box-folder 26-20)
  - STS-2 Orbiter Mission Report, February 1982 (Box-folder 26-21)
  - Personal Notes, March 1982 (Box-folder 26-22)
  - STS-3 Debriefing, April 6, 1982 (Box-folder 26-23)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Charter, Rice University, April 29, 1982 (Box-folder 26-24)
  - Personal Notes, April 1982 (Box-folder 26-25)
  - Annual Meeting of Houston Chamber of Commerce, May 13, 1982 (Box-folder 26-26)
  - AIAA 50th Anniversary, Teague Auditorium, May 21, 1982 (Box-folder 26-27)
  - Personal Notes, May 1982 (Box-folder 26-28)
  - Personal Notes, June 1982 (Box-folder 26-29)